A Guide to the Mary-Cooke Branch Munford Papers, 1881-1935
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Virginia's Attitude Toward Slavery and Secession
  - Subseries 1: Subject Files
    - Virginia's Attitude Toward Slavery and Secession-Gallery Proof (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
    - Virginia Book Company (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - W (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Williams Printing Company (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Subject Files
  - Accounts, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, 1926-1931 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bottomley, William Lawrence, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Child Labor (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Child Welfare League (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Churches and World Peace (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Community Fund (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Consumer's League (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Committees, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Publicity (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Women's Luncheon Club, 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 1926-1927 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Grace Street Property, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Houston, Harry R.- Photographs, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Kahn Fellowship, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Notebook of B.B. Munford, 1881-1885 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Patriotic Community League of Loudoun County (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Patriotic League (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Southern Aid Society of Virginia, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Social Work (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Speakers, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Women's Democratic News, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Y.W.C.A., 1927 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings File (Box 29, Folder 1-17)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 30)